<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Sword and Tower Games</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Sword and Tower Games</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 24 Jun 2022 22:11:15 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>I Played ICRPG Part Three</title>
      <link>/blog/iplayedicrpgpart3/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jun 2022 22:11:15 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/iplayedicrpgpart3/</guid>
      <description>This past Monday, I played ICRPG, and here&amp;rsquo;s what happened. For those of you who may not have heard of ICRPG, it&amp;rsquo;s a tabletop roleplaying game created by Runehammer! ICRPG is very rules-light and built to be hacked into what you like. It provides excellent scaffolding for three different worlds to play in, each with its unique classes, loot, enemies, maps, and more. The rules are so small you can learn them in something like ten minutes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Played ICRPG Part Two</title>
      <link>/blog/iplayedicrpgpart2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jun 2022 17:46:55 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/iplayedicrpgpart2/</guid>
      <description>Early Thursday morning, I played ICRPG, and here&amp;rsquo;s what happened. For those of you who may not have heard of ICRPG, it&amp;rsquo;s a tabletop roleplaying game created by Runehammer! ICRPG is very rules-light and built to be hacked into what you like. It provides excellent scaffolding for three different worlds to play in, each with its unique classes, loot, enemies, maps, and more. The rules are so small you can learn them in something like ten minutes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Played ICRPG</title>
      <link>/blog/iplayedicrpg/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 17:46:55 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/iplayedicrpg/</guid>
      <description>This past Monday evening, I played ICRPG, and here&amp;rsquo;s what happened. For those of you who may not have heard of ICRPG, it&amp;rsquo;s a tabletop roleplaying game created by Runehammer! ICRPG is very rules-light and built to be hacked into what you like. It provides excellent scaffolding for three different worlds to play in, each with its unique classes, loot, enemies, maps, and more. The rules are so small you can learn them in something like ten minutes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Weekly Work Lunch Game, Part One</title>
      <link>/blog/thebeneathpart1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2022 17:46:55 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/thebeneathpart1/</guid>
      <description>For over five years, I&amp;rsquo;ve worked at a tech startup writing code. During that time, I&amp;rsquo;ve had the pleasure to run a game of Dungeons and Dragons fifth edition for my coworkers during our lunch break. Many of those players had their first experience with tabletop RPGs at our one-hour-long games. So far, we&amp;rsquo;ve been playing almost every week for five straight years. This series is a recap of our adventures, the drama, and the communal storytelling we&amp;rsquo;ve shared in a world that I&amp;rsquo;ve called &amp;ldquo;The Beneath.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2022 17:11:47 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>For nearly two decades I have been running tabletop RPGs like D&amp;amp;D. Ever since a middle school teacher introduced me to 2nd edition Dungeons and Dragons, I was hooked. In the back of history class, I&amp;rsquo;d run a small game for a group of anti-authority friends. We smashed down doors, explored dungeons, fought orcs, and found treasure. Soon, I was off to college and bigger groups and long-lasting campaigns.
I was inspired by Hank at Runehammerto share what I&amp;rsquo;ve been working on with the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2022 17:11:47 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/contact/</guid>
      <description>Feel free to send an email to stephen@swordandtower.com or hit me up on Instagram @swordandtower!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tomb of Kor</title>
      <link>/portfolio/tombofkor/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2022 17:11:47 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/portfolio/tombofkor/</guid>
      <description>The Tomb of Kor is a short dungeon packed with traps, secrets, and treasure. Kor’s Tomb is intended to be a short adventure for low- to medium-level characters and is especially good at providing some opportunities for extra loot and creative problem-solving.
This adventure is suitable for any D20 type system and can be easily translated. At the end of the adventure is a list of magic items/treasures that can be found inside the Tomb.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
